vfreshers.com 2018-02-21

# Privacy Policy | Freshers Jobs India

**Privacy Policy for www.vfreshers.com**

At www.vfreshers.com, the privacy of our visitors is of utmost importance to us. This privacy policy gives details on what kind of personal information is received and collected by www.vfreshers.com and how do we use/safeguard that information.

Log Files  
www.vfreshers.com makes use of the data contained in log files like most of the other websites. This data includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of website browsers( such as Internet explorer or Firefox or chrome), Internet Service Provider( ISP like Airtel or Tata Indicom ), date/time stamp of user’s visites, entry/exit pages, number of pageviews per use & and total number of users to gather statistics about the website’s users in order to administer the site effectively.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
www.vfreshers.com does use cookies to store information about user’s preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

DoubleClick DART Cookie  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.vfreshers.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.vfreshers.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.vfreshers.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

If have any questions about our privacy policy or you need more information, please feel free to email us at vfreshers[at]gmail[dot]com
